

Portugal

+351 926 843 295

franciscoandre.farp@gmail.com

My Portfolio in ffarps.github.io

My linkedin

# **OBJECTIVE**

My name is Francisco André Rodrigues Pereira, I'm 22 years old, from Mirandela, and I graduated from the Polytechnic Institute of Braganca with a degree in Informatics Engineering.

During the third year of the course and after completing it, I was awarded two research grants by the Centre for Research in Digitalisation and Intelligent Robotics (CeDRI).

Proactive and dedicated, ready to achieve great things.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Jul 2023-Sep 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Contributed to an OpenZDM project related to developing a C# and OpenGl-based tool in Unity 3D, that aims to reduce defects in production chains in a car factory in the assembly and body shop zones.

Jul 2022-Jan 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Worked on developing Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) apps in Unity, using different frameworks and tools, such as MRTK, ARCore, Vuforia SDK and ARFoundation.

## **EDUCATION**

Oct 2019-Jul 2023 **Degree in Informatics Engineering**  Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Scientific Areas: Computer Science, Computer Engineering, Mathematics, Information Systems. Worked on many projects related to Web Development, Computer Architecture, Networking, 3D Modeling, Machine Learning, Data Structures, SQL and IoT.

2016-2019

**High School Diploma** Science and technology Agrupamento de Escolas de Mirandela

#### LANGUAGES

#### HARD SKILLS

Portuguese - native English - proficient

Programming: C#, Python, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, etc Source Control: Git

Linux and Bash Unity 3D

Databases: SQL and NoSQL

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Self-taught Attention to detail **Technical Writing** Teamwork